estarland.com 2014-08-26

# eStarland Privacy / Security Policy - Video Games & Anime Merchandise

Privacy and Security Statement

**Your privacy and security is our number one concern. **

**

* * *

Privacy Statement**

eStarland.com takes the privacy of our customer’s information very seriously. Our Privacy Policy outlines how any personal information you submit to eStarland.com will be used. We want your shopping experience to be worry-free. To that end, we are committed to protecting the privacy rights of all visitors to eStarland.com. 

**We will not sell or give your e-mail address or personal information to any third party** and any personal information received through Live Support will be kept strictly confidential. 

Data collected at eStarland.com provides us with demographic information that helps us improve the site and allows us to serve you better. 

If at any time you would no longer like to take part in our newsletter program, simply e-mail us via the address that is provided at the bottom of any newsletter that we send to you with the UNSUBSCRIBE command and you will be taken off of the list within ten business days. If you are a member of eStarland.com, simply login to your account and click on the Newsletter checkbox to deselect it. 

In order to conduct business, eStarland.com must gather certain personal information from its customers. The following section details how this information is used. 

When an order is placed, a customer’s contact information is used to process the order and to communicate order information such as shipping details. It is also used to communicate release date changes on reserved titles and to respond to requests for additional information. 

Communication through e-mail also includes an optional newsletter, notifications of special offers, customer surveys, and other promotional notifications. These e-mails are optional and can be unsubscribed at the discretion of the customer. 

The eStarland site utilizes alphanumeric identifiers called " **Cookies** " in the operation of our commerce engine. These are placed on your computers hard drive through your web browser and enable our site to recognize your system’s browser on future visits. Cookies can be blocked or screened through browser options at the discretion of the customer. However, if cookies are blocked, eStarland will not be able to function. In order to shop at eStarland.com, customers must have cookies enabled. 

While eStarland guards your information, it is important to keep your own computer secure. Anyone who has access to your computer may be able to view your information at eStarland, so it is important to protect your login and password information. 

**

* * *

eStarland.com Site Security Statement**

The security of all Transactions at eStarland.com is a top priority for our business. Our website is protected with **Go Daddy's 256-bit encryption technology** , which allows you to enjoy **the strongest possible online security** to assure that your credit card information and personal details are kept secure. You can shop with assurance that your order will be safe with us. 

Information that is received by eStarland is transmitted via Secure Sockets Layer technology and is stored on our secure server. The checkout page is a secure site that protects your personal information. 

All payments are processed with secure payments technology through Authorize.net. Financial Information is protected with high-level encryption and is kept secure through every step of the process. 

**

* * *

****Safe Shopping Guarantee**

Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank cannot hold you liable for more than $50.00 of fraudulent charges. If your bank does hold you liable for any of this $50.00, eStarland.com will cover the entire liability for you, up to the full $50.00. eStarland.com will only cover this liability if the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own from purchases made at eStarland.com while using the secure server. 

In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures.
